The Mainprice Deposit
The Mainprice Deposit
- Documents relating to the Astley-Nicholson family of Dukinfield, co Ches, 1779-1913; GB/418/E.8.1-E.8.2; GB/418/Main/3; 204 files; Chetham's Library
  - Documents concerning Francis Dukinfield Astley, 1779-1879; GB/418/E.8.1-2 (1-174); GB/418/Main/3/1; 147 files; Chetham's Library
    - Release of a plot of land in Dukinfield with a reservation of the yearly rent of £93 1s 10½d and the mines under the same plot, 2 Sep 1836; GB/418/E.8.1-2 (43); GB/418/Main/3/1/35; Chetham's Library
      Demises in trust of the late F.D. Astley and mortgagees to Charles Hindley
    - Duplicate release of a plot of land in Dukinfield with a reservation of the yearly rent of £31 4s 7d and the mines under the same plot, 2 Sep 1836; GB/418/E.8.1-2 (44); GB/418/Main/3/1/36; Chetham's Library
      Demises in trust of the late F.D. Astley and mortgagees to Jeol Gee
    - Release of a plot of land in Dukinfield with a reservation of the yearly rent of £8 10 s 8d and the mines under the same plot, 2 Nov 1836; GB/418/E.8.1-2 (45 & 46); GB/418/Main/3/1/37; 2 items; Chetham's Library
      Demises in trust of the late F.D. Astley and mortgagees to George Walshaw
    - Mortgage by appointment and demise of a plot of land and several messuages or dwelling houses in Dukinfield, 5 Jul 1837; GB/418/E.8.1-2 (47); GB/418/Main/3/1/38; Chetham's Library
      From George Walshaw to James Siddall.
      For the term of 1000 years upon trust to sell for securing £400 and interest.
    - Assignment of a plot of land and several messuages or dwelling houses in Dukinfield for the residue of a mortgage term, 6 Jul 1837; GB/418/E.8.1-2 (48); GB/418/Main/3/1/39; Chetham's Library
      From George Walshaw to Mr and Mrs Clarke.
      Ripon Trust to sell as an additional security for £500 and subject to a poor mortgage.
    - Duplicate release of 3 several plots of land in Dukinfield with a reservation of the yearly rent of £93 15s 5d and the mines under the same plot, 3 Apr 1838; GB/418/E.8.1-2 (49); GB/418/Main/3/1/40; Chetham's Library
      Demises in trust of the late F.D. Astley and mortgagees to John Wagstaff
    - Transfer of mortgage on premises in Dukinfield to secure £400 and interest, 15 Jan 1839; GB/418/E.8.1-2 (50); GB/418/Main/3/1/41; Chetham's Library
      From George Walshaw and his mortgagees to Mrs Clarke
    - Duplicate demise of a plot of land in Dukinfield for a term of 2000 years to a yearly rent of £9 7s 6d, 20 Jul 1839; GB/418/E.8.1-2 (51); GB/418/Main/3/1/42; Chetham's Library
      Demises in trust and the mortgagees of the late F.D. Astley to William Revines
    - Assignment of certain tenements and premises in Dukinfield, 11 Jan 1844; GB/418/E.8.1-2 (52); GB/418/Main/3/1/43; Chetham's Library
      Misses Mary Buckley and Betty Buckley to John Boulton
    - Release of a plot of land in Dukinfield with a reservation of the yearly rent of £8 18s 4d, 9 Oct 1845; GB/418/E.8.1-2 (53); GB/418/Main/3/1/44; Chetham's Library
      Demises etc to Horatio Rains
    - Mortgage by appointment and demise of certain hereditaments and premises situated in Newton, 28 Nov 1845; GB/418/E.8.1-2 (54); GB/418/Main/3/1/45; Chetham's Library
      Horatio Rains to Isaac Linney.
      For a term of 500 years with power to sell for securing £150 and interest.
    - Conveyance in fee of 4 messuages or dwelling houses situate in Dukinfield subject to a moiety or half part of a chief of £2 10s 9d, 2 Jun 1846; GB/418/E.8.1-2 (55); GB/418/Main/3/1/46; Chetham's Library
      Thomas Hadfield, demise in trust for sale under the will of Robert Schofield, deceased, to Abel Buckley Wimpenny
    - Assignment of certain premises at Newton, 23 Oct 1846; GB/418/E.8.1-2 (56); GB/418/Main/3/1/47; Chetham's Library
      From Isaac Linney to Betty Ogden.
      Consideration: £180.
    - Mortgage of hereditaments at Newton with power to sell for securing £200 and interest, 24 Oct 1846; GB/418/E.8.1-2 (57); GB/418/Main/3/1/48; Chetham's Library
      From Betty Ogden to Jane Ogden
    - Assignment of premises situate near the aquaduct in Dukinfield with the buildings thereon erected, 29 Oct 1846; GB/418/E.8.1-2 (58); GB/418/Main/3/1/49; Chetham's Library
      Assignes of John Boulton, a bankrupt, and John Boulton to Isaac W. Boulton
    - Conveyance of a plot of land situate in Dukinfield subject to rent charge of £11 3s 7½d, 1 Dec 1847; GB/418/E.8.1-2 (59 & 60); GB/418/Main/3/1/50; 2 items; Chetham's Library
      F.D.P. Astley to W[illia]m Dean and W[illia]m Tinker.
      With duplicate copy.
    - Release of a plot of land in Dukinfield in the county of Chester with a reservation of a yearly rent of £14 17s 4d, 8 Feb 1849; GB/418/E.8.1-2 (61 & 62); GB/418/Main/3/1/51; 2 items; Chetham's Library
      Francis Dukinfield P. Astley esq to Messrs James Warbrick and W[illia]m Warbrick.
    - Assignment of a leasehold plot of land, buildings and premises in Dukinfield, 30 Nov 1850; GB/418/E.8.1-2 (63); GB/418/Main/3/1/52; Chetham's Library
      From Isaac Watt Boulton to John Boulton.
      Consideration: £200.
    - Demise of a plot of land in Dukinfield for 2000 years, 12 Apr 1852; GB/418/E.8.1-2 (64 & 65); GB/418/Main/3/1/53; Chetham's Library
      Devises in trust under the will of the late Mr Howard and their mortgagee to Josiah Hill.
      Yearly rent £5 19s 8d.
    - Duplicate conveyance in fee of a plot of land in Dukinfield with a reservation of an annual chief rent of £1 12s 5d, 13 Apr 1852; GB/418/E.8.1-2 (66); GB/418/Main/3/1/54; Chetham's Library
      From Francis Dukinfield Palmer Astley to C.F. Hindley
    - Surrender of a plot of land fronting Grasscroft Street in Stalybridge, 16 Aug 1852; GB/418/E.8.1-2 (67); GB/418/Main/3/1/55; Chetham's Library
      From John Bradbury and his mortgagee to F.D.P. Astley
    - Release of a plot of land in Dukinfield with a reservation of a chief rent of £30 5s 1½d, 31 Aug 1852; GB/418/E.8.1-2 (68); GB/418/Main/3/1/56; Chetham's Library
      From Francis Dukinfield Palmer Astley to John Gartside Jnr
    - Conveyance in fee of a plot of land in Dukinfield with a reservation of an annual chief rent of £12 1s 6d, 28 Sep 1852; GB/418/E.8.1-2 (69); GB/418/Main/3/1/57; Chetham's Library
      From Francis Dukinfield Palmer Astley to Charles and James Fernihough
    - Conveyance in fee of a plot of land in Dukinfield with a reservation of an annual chief rent of £6 18s 6d, 19 Nov 1852; GB/418/E.8.1-2 (70); GB/418/Main/3/1/58; Chetham's Library
      From Francis Dukinfield Palmer Astley to John Swindells
    - Mortgage in fee of a plot of land and 7 messuages thereon situate in Dukinfield, 29 Nov 1852; GB/418/E.8.1-2 (71); GB/418/Main/3/1/59; Chetham's Library
      From John Swindells to Ralph Ogden.
      Upon trust for sale to secure £180 and interest.
    - Conveyance in fee of a plot of land in Dukinfield with a reservation of an annual chief rent of £7 6s 8d, 29 Dec 1852; GB/418/E.8.1-2 (72); GB/418/Main/3/1/60; Chetham's Library
      From Francis Dukinfield Palmer Astley to Josiah Hill
    - Duplicate deed of covenants as to land and water in Walmsley Street and Grasscroft Street in Stalybridge in Dukinfield, 31 Dec 1852; GB/418/E.8.1-2 (73); GB/418/Main/3/1/61; Chetham's Library
      Francis Dukinfield Palmer Astley and John Bradbury and his mortgagee
    - Conveyance of two plots of land at Dukinfield in the county of Chester with a reservation of a chief rent of £94 14s 6d, 10 Jun 1853; GB/418/E.8.1-2 (74 & 75); GB/418/Main/3/1/62; 2 items; Chetham's Library
      From Francis Dukinfield Palmer Astley Esqr to Mr John Shaw.
      This deed was surrendered by deed dated 8 Dec 1855.
    - Conveyance in fee of a plot of land in Dukinfield in the county of Chester, with a reservation of an annual rent of £51 9s 2d, 20 Aug 1853; GB/418/E.8.1-2 (76); GB/418/Main/3/1/63; Chetham's Library
      From F.D.P. Astley Esqr to Mr William Warbrick
    - Conveyance in fee of a plot of land in Dukinfield with a reservation of an annual chief rent of £10 4s 0d, 13 Dec 1853; GB/418/E.8.1-2 (77); GB/418/Main/3/1/64; Chetham's Library
    - Duplicate lease of a plot of land in Newton for 2000 years with a reservation of a chief rent of £2 14s 4d, 16 Sep 1854; GB/418/E.8.1-2 (78); GB/418/Main/3/1/65; Chetham's Library
      From Francis Dukinfield Palmer Astley esq to W[illia]m Hinchcliffe
    - Conveyance of a plot of land in Dukinfield with a reservation of an annual chief rent of £23 8s 0d, 30 Dec 1854; GB/418/E.8.1-2 (79 & 80); GB/418/Main/3/1/66; 2 items; Chetham's Library
      Francis Dukinfield Palmer Astley to M.D. Thompson.
    - Duplicate release of two several plots of land in Dukinfield with a reservation of the yearly rent of £90 14s 1½d and the mines under the same plots, 5 Aug 1855; GB/418/E.8.1-2 (81); GB/418/Main/3/1/67; Chetham's Library
      Devises in trust of the late Francis Dukinfield Astley and mortgagees to Robert Ashton
    - Deed for vesting certain rent charges in trustees as a collateral security against substituting life annuities, 13 Oct 1855; GB/418/E.8.1-2 (82); GB/418/Main/3/1/68; Chetham's Library
      From Francis Dukinfield Palmer Astley to Messrs Clabon and Gisbourne
    - Deed of covenant for production of title deeds, 13 Oct 1855; GB/418/E.8.1-2 (83); GB/418/Main/3/1/69; Chetham's Library
      From Thomas Hankey and George Hankey and F.D.P. Astley to Mary and Caroline Chatfield
    - Surrender of two plots of land and the buildings thereon in Dukinfield and release by the said F.D.P. Astley of the chief rent to which such property is subject, 8 Dec 1855; GB/418/E.8.1-2 (84); GB/418/Main/3/1/70; Chetham's Library
      From John Shaw and his mortgagees and trustee to Francis Dukinfield Palmer Astley
    - Assignment of two several plots of land situate in Dukinfield for the residue of two several terms of 2000 years and 20000 years therein, 26 Dec 1855; GB/418/E.8.1-2 (85 & 86); GB/418/Main/3/1/71; Chetham's Library
      Revd James Crook and others to Francis Dukinfield Palmer Astley.
    - Conveyance in fee of a plot of land in Dukinfield with a reservation of an annual chief rent of £9 0s 9d, 10 Mar 1856; GB/418/E.8.1-2 (87); GB/418/Main/3/1/72; Chetham's Library
      From Francis Dukinfield Palmer Astley to James Fernihough.
      Reconveyance of the same plot of land and extinguishing of the said rent.
    - Mortgage of a freehold plot of land and the buildings thereon at Dukinfield with power of sale for securing £270 and interest, 9 Sep 1856; GB/418/E.8.1-2 (88); GB/418/Main/3/1/73; Chetham's Library
      From John Swindells and his trustee to Ralph Ogden
    - Conveyance of a plot of land in Dukinfield with a reservation of an annual chief rent of £124 0s 3d, 13 Nov 1856; GB/418/E.8.1-2 (89 & 90); GB/418/Main/3/1/74; 2 items; Chetham's Library
      From Francis Dukinfield Palmer Astley to Charles Hindley.
    - Duplicate lease of Black Mine and other coals in Dukinfield for 21 years, 15 Nov 1856; GB/418/E.8.1-2 (91); GB/418/Main/3/1/75; Chetham's Library
      From Francis Dukinfield Palmer Astley to G. J. Newton and others
    - Duplicate lease of the Great and Roger Mines in Dukinfield, 15 Nov 1856; GB/418/E.8.1-2 (92); GB/418/Main/3/1/76; Chetham's Library
    - Conveyance in fee of a plot of land in Dukinfield with reservation of an annual chief rent of £20 0s 0d, 16 Dec 1856; GB/418/E.8.1-2 (93); GB/418/Main/3/1/77; Chetham's Library
      From Francis Dukinfield Palmer Astley to Aaron Ogden
    - Release of a plot of land situate in Dukinfield Hall subject to the yearly rent of £31 4s 7d, 3 Jan 1857; GB/418/E.8.1-2 (94); GB/418/Main/3/1/78; Chetham's Library
      From Charles Hindley and his trustee to William Travis
    - Reconveyance of a freehold plot of land in Dukinfield and release by F.D.P. Astley of the chief rent to which such plot of land was previously subject, 17 Mar 1857; GB/418/E.8.1-2 (95); GB/418/Main/3/1/79; Chetham's Library
      From John Gartside Jnr to Francis Dukinfield Palmer Astley
    - Conveyance of a plot of land in Dukinfield with a reservation of an annual chief rent of £22 10s 0d, 27 Nov 1857; GB/418/E.8.1-2 (96 & 97); GB/418/Main/3/1/80; 2 items; Chetham's Library
      From Francis Dukinfield Palmer Astley to Moses Davenport Thompson.
    - Probate of the will of Mr John Swindells decd, 1858; GB/418/E.8.1-2 (98); GB/418/Main/3/1/81; Chetham's Library
    - Conveyance of a plot of land and the buildings thereon in Staley, 26 Apr 1858; GB/418/E.8.1-2 (99); GB/418/Main/3/1/82; Chetham's Library
      From Rt Hon the Earl of Stamford and Warrington to Robert Platt.
      Consideration: £300.
    - Conveyance of a plot of land in Dukinfield with a reservation of an annual chief rent of £30 1s 6d, 10 Feb 1859; GB/418/E.8.1-2 (100 & 101); GB/418/Main/3/1/83; 2 items; Chetham's Library
      From Francis Dukinfield Palmer Astley to Moses Davenport Thompson
    - Conveyance of freehold land situate in Dukinfield, 2 Aug 1859; GB/418/E.8.1-2 (102); GB/418/Main/3/1/84; Chetham's Library
      From Francis Dukinfield Palmer Astley to Robert Platt
    - Assignment of a plot of land and the messuages or dwelling houses thereon situate in Dukinfield, 23 Dec 1859; GB/418/E.8.1-2 (103); GB/418/Main/3/1/85; Chetham's Library
      From Mary Clarke to Abel Beaumont.
      Consideration: £421.
    - Conveyance of a plot of land and the buildings thereon in Dukinfield and release by F.D.P. Astley of the chief rent and covenants to which such plot of land was previously subject, 10 Feb 1860; GB/418/E.8.1-2 (104); GB/418/Main/3/1/86; Chetham's Library
      From George Walshaw and Abel Beaumont to F.D.P. Astley
    - Conveyance in fee of a plot of land in Dukinfield with a reservation of an annual chief rent of £3 2s 6d, 20 Jun 1860; GB/418/E.8.1-2 (105 & 106); GB/418/Main/3/1/87; 2 items; Chetham's Library
      From Francis Dukinfield Palmer Astley to Samuel Smith
    - Disclaimer by Mr Thomas Delamere of Dukinfield of his Trusteeship under the will of the late John Swindells of Dukinfield, 24 Oct 1860; GB/418/E.8.1-2 (107); GB/418/Main/3/1/88; Chetham's Library
    - Conveyance in fee of two plots of land and the messuages or dwelling houses thereon erected in Dukinfield, 7 Nov 1860; GB/418/E.8.1-2 (108); GB/418/Main/3/1/89; Chetham's Library
      Devises in trust under the will of the late John Swindells and his mortgagee to John Kirk.
      Consideration: £650.
    - Mortgage in fee of two plots of land and the dwelling houses thereon situate at Dukinfield with power of sale for securing £450 and interest, 8 Nov 1860; GB/418/E.8.1-2 (109); GB/418/Main/3/1/90; Chetham's Library
      From John Kirk to Ralph Ogden
    - Demise of a plot of land, buildings and premises at Newton Wood in Dukinfield subject to yearly rent of £12 5 2, 17 Jul 1851; GB/418/E.8.1-2 (110); GB/418/Main/3/1/91; Chetham's Library
      From Newton Moor Cotton Spinning Co Ltd to Francis Dukinfield Palmer Astley
    - Lease of a brick yard in Dukinfield and license to get clay etc out of several plots of land adjoining thereto at Birches in Dukinfield, 25 Mar 1861; GB/418/E.8.1-2 (111); GB/418/Main/3/1/92; Chetham's Library
      From Francis Dukinfield Palmer Astley esq to The Dukinfield Brick and Tile Manufacturing Company Ltd.
      This deed surrendered by Richard Brierley, Tho[ma]s [?Milliannerio] and William Ogden, 9 Oct 1866.
    - Duplicate conveyance in fee of a plot of land in Dukinfield with a reservation of an annual chief rent of £2 2s 0d, 19 Oct 1861; GB/418/E.8.1-2 (112); GB/418/Main/3/1/93; Chetham's Library
      From Francis Dukinfield Palmer Astley to Samuel Varley
    - Conveyance in fee of a plot of land in Dukinfield with a reservation of an annual chief rent of £11 2s 1d, 20 Dec 1861; GB/418/E.8.1-2 (113 & 114); GB/418/Main/3/1/94; 2 items; Chetham's Library
      From Francis Dukinfield Palmer Astley to James Farnsworth.
    - Conveyance in fee of a plot of land in Dukinfield with a reservation of an annual chief rent of £17 1s 2d, 14 May 1862; GB/418/E.8.1-2 (115); GB/418/Main/3/1/95; Chetham's Library
      From Francis Dukinfield Palmer Astley to Andrew and George Robert Ray
    - Conveyance in fee of a plot of land in Dukinfield with a reservation of an annual chief rent of £4 8s 11½d, 19 Dec 1863; GB/418/E.8.1-2 (116); GB/418/Main/3/1/96; Chetham's Library
      From Allen Harrop to Alfred Harrop
    - Conveyance in fee of a plot of land in Dukinfield with a reservation of an annual chief rent of £3 0d 4s and reconveyance of the premises and release of the said F.D.P. Astley of the rent and covenants, 30 Dec 1865; GB/418/E.8.1-2 (117 & 118); GB/418/Main/3/1/97; 2 items; Chetham's Library
      Consideration: £58.
      Francis Dukinfield Palmer Astley to James Ogden.
    - Conveyance in fee of a plot of land and buildings in Dukinfield and surrender of a term of years thereon, 23 Feb 1866; GB/418/E.8.1-2 (119); GB/418/Main/3/1/98; Chetham's Library
      From Assignes of Horatio Rains and others to Francis Dukinfield Palmer Astley
    - Duplicate conveyance of a piece of land in Tame Valley Road, Dukinfield, and release or deferance of certain covenants contained in a prior deed in consideration of assent being given to interments in the Ashton under Lyne cemetery within 100 yards of the Grantees buildings, 9 Nov 1866; GB/418/E.8.1-2 (120); GB/418/Main/3/1/99; Chetham's Library
      From Francis Dukinfield Palmer Astley at the request of the Mayor, Aldermen and Burgesses of the Borough of Ashton under Lyne to Thomas Naylor and James Hall, mortgagees of Mr Johnson.
    - Duplicate conveyance in fee for three plots of land in Dukinfield with a reservation of an annual chief rent of £28 12s 0d, 10 Nov 1866; GB/418/E.8.1-2 (121); GB/418/Main/3/1/100; Chetham's Library
      From Francis Dukinfield Palmer Astley to James Fernihough
    - Mortgage in fee of a plot of land, smithy workshop and buildings, machinery and premises situate in Dukinfield with power of sale for securing £250 and interest, 27 Apr 1867; GB/418/E.8.1-2 (122); GB/418/Main/3/1/101; Chetham's Library
      From Andrew Ray and George Robert Ray to Joseph Beard
    - Mutual conveyances of land in Newton and Hyde and grants of rights of way over an intended street dividing their estates, 24 Jun 1867; GB/418/E.8.1-2 (123); GB/418/Main/3/1/102; Chetham's Library
      From Francis Dukinfield Palmer Astley and Thomas Ashton
    - Reconveyance of three several plots of land and hereditaments, situate in Dukinfield and release by Mr Astley of the rents and covenants relating thereto, 4 Oct 1867; GB/418/E.8.1-2 (124); GB/418/Main/3/1/103; Chetham's Library
      From Moses Davenport Thompson to F.D.P. Astley
    - Transfer of mortgage debt of £250 secured with interest at £5% per annum upon a plot of land, smithy workshop buildings and premises situate at Dukinfield, 15 Jul 1868; GB/418/E.8.1-2 (125); GB/418/Main/3/1/104; Chetham's Library
      Joseph Beard by the direction of Andrew and George Robert Ray
    - Further charge of a plot of land, smithy workshop and buildings, machinery and premises situate in Dukinfield to secure £100 and interest in addition to £250 previously advanced, 11 Sep 1868; GB/418/E.8.1-2 (126); GB/418/Main/3/1/105; Chetham's Library
      From Andrew Ray and George Robert Ray to Arthur Buckley.
    - Conveyance of a plot of land in Dukinfield subject to a perpetual yearly rent of £5 17s 4d, 25 Dec 1869; GB/418/E.8.1-2 (127 & 128); GB/418/Main/3/1/106; Chetham's Library
      From the Trustees under the will of Francis Dukinfield Palmer Astley, decd, to Michael Coffey.
    - Conveyance of a plot of land situate in Dukinfield subject to a perpetual yearly rent of £5 14s 2d, 6 Jun 1870; GB/418/E.8.1-2 (129 & 130); GB/418/Main/3/1/107; 2 items; Chetham's Library
      From the Trustees under the will of Francis Dukinfield Palmer Astley, decd, to John Hampson.
    - Duplicate conveyance of a plot of land in Dukinfield subject to a perpetual yearly rent of £14 17s 8d, 30 Jun 1870; GB/418/E.8.1-2 (131); GB/418/Main/3/1/108; Chetham's Library
      From the Trustees under the will of Francis Dukinfield Palmer Astley, decd, to Thomas Beeley.
    - Mortgage in fee of a plot of land, dwelling house and premises in Dukinfield to secure £500 and interest, 5 Aug 1870; GB/418/E.8.1-2 (132); GB/418/Main/3/1/109; Chetham's Library
      From Aaron Ogden to Martha Hesketh
    - Abstract of the Manchester and County Bank Ltd to a plot of land, cotton mill or factory, messuage or dwelling house and other buildings situate at Newton Ward co Ches contracted to be sold to Thomas Beeley, 1871; GB/418/E.8.1-2 (133); GB/418/Main/3/1/110; Chetham's Library
    - Conveyance of a plot of land and the smithy workshop building and premises erected thereon situated in Dukinfield, 19 Jun 1871; GB/418/E.8.1-2 (134); GB/418/Main/3/1/111; Chetham's Library
      From Arthur Buckley to Rev William Heffill
    - Conveyance in fee of a plot of land in Dukinfield, 18 Jul 1871; GB/418/E.8.1-2 (135); GB/418/Main/3/1/112; Chetham's Library
      From C. W. Travis to the Rt Hon William Frederick Aaron Abinger and Sir W. Jones, bart
    - Conveyance of a plot of land in Dukinfield subject to a perpetual yearly rent of £1 2s 0d, 9 Sep 1871; GB/418/E.8.1-2 (136); GB/418/Main/3/1/113; Chetham's Library
      Trustees under the will of Francis Dukinfield Palmer Astley to John Smith
    - Duplicate conveyance of a dwelling house at Chapel Hill, Dukinfield, 11 Jan 1872; GB/418/E.8.1-2 (137); GB/418/Main/3/1/114; Chetham's Library
      From Charles Harrop and others to Anne Elizabeth Harrop.
      Duplicate conveyance of a plot of land in Dukinfield and release of a chief rent.
    - Grant of a plot of land in Dukinfield subject to an annual rent charge of £19 8s 8d, 8 Sep 1874; GB/418/E.8.1-2 (138 & 139); GB/418/Main/3/1/115; 2 items; Chetham's Library
      From Francis Dukinfield Astley to William Lynham.
    - Conveyance of an individual 17th part or share of lands in two closes of land situate at Sandiacre, co Derbys, 30 Jan 1875; GB/418/E.8.1-2 (140); GB/418/Main/3/1/116; Chetham's Library
      From John Renato to F.D. Astley
    - Conveyance of a plot of land and 8 messuages thereon fronting Forrester Street, Stalybridge, co Ches, 4 Mar 1875; GB/418/E.8.1-2 (141); GB/418/Main/3/1/117; Chetham's Library
      From the Devisees in trust of Sarah Heginbottom, decd, to Mr Joseph Sandbach.
      Yearly rent: £14 7s 0d.
      Consideration: £355.
    - Mortgage in fee of a plot of land and eight messuages thereon fronting Forrester Street, Stalybridge, 5 Mar 1875; GB/418/E.8.1-2 (142); GB/418/Main/3/1/118; Chetham's Library
      From Joseph Sandbach to the trustees of the Royal Permanent Building Society
    - Duplicate grant of a plot of land in Newton subject to an annual rent charge of £9 10s 4d, 15 Apr 1875; GB/418/E.8.1-2 (143); GB/418/Main/3/1/119; Chetham's Library
      From Francis Dukinfield Astley to Josiah Perrin
    - Conveyance in fee of a plot of land in Dukinfield subject to an annual rent of £3 2s 6d, 12 May 1875; GB/418/E.8.1-2 (144); GB/418/Main/3/1/120; Chetham's Library
      From Mary Smith and others to F.D.P. Astley
    - Conveyance of lands and hereditaments in Dukinfield, 10 Aug 1875; GB/418/E.8.1-2 (145); GB/418/Main/3/1/121; Chetham's Library
      From Robert Platt to F.D. Astley
    - Covenant for production of deeds relating to the title of lands etc in Staley and Matley, 10 Aug 1875; GB/418/E.8.1-2 (146); GB/418/Main/3/1/122; Chetham's Library
    - Conveyance of lands in Staley and Matley, 10 Aug 1875; GB/418/E.8.1-2 (147); GB/418/Main/3/1/123; Chetham's Library
    - Conveyance of two several plots of land and the messuages or dwelling houses thereon situate in Dukinfield, 15 Sep 1875; GB/418/E.8.1-2 (148); GB/418/Main/3/1/124; Chetham's Library
      From Ralph Ogden, Joseph Ogden and John Ogden (trustees of Ralph Ogden, decd) to Richard Barnes.
      Consideration £675.